The second value like
that. And then the third one we need to add is a CNAME record.
So we just need to go to C name. It needs
a www as the host and
we just post that in there like that. We're going to save changes.
So currently these are the three records needed for web flow.
Now if you have already done your Facebook prep you will also
have a Facebook verification encode in here which will be a.
Txt record. It will look a little like that and
then you'll have your I believe it does use an app and then you'll have
a Facebook verification code which will be something like Facebook
verification equals and then it
will be a string of numbers like that. You can get this from Facebook and
I would advise if you haven't done this already, you will need to do it
because we need the Pixel code that you'd have made from that training as well.
So I do recommend going back and doing the Facebook prep if you've got
to this point so far, I'm just going to cancel that because I don't need
to add that record. So once we've got these three records added now these can
take a little bit of time to propagate.
It can take up to 72 hours to propagate but that is very
uncommon. You will notice here I'm going to go
back into web flow and on these two things. Now I need to check status
and as you can see mine has already gone through. So that's the first one
done. Then we're going to hit check status on the second one and there we
go is done. So now this domain is completely added and
that's what I mean is generally most domains will happen almost
instantaneously depending on the host you're using. The reason we recommend Name Cheap
is because it is a very good host. It is very fast, but if you're
using something like GoDaddy or whatever it can take longer and it is recommended
like an industry standard that it can take all the way up to 72 hours
but it is fairly rare. So once that's done
and we've made the www default, we're going to head over to the
editor settings. Now inside Editor We don't really need to do
anything. What you can do change is you can change the logo here to
your company, but it doesn't really matter because you're not really going to be handing
out your editor status at all anyway. Inside Billing is
where you'll see all your billing so you can keep up to date on how
it's working and what subscriptions is where you cancel through site Plan upgrade your site
plan it's fine. Past invoices Inside SEO
what.